[♪♪♪]
[MONSTERS GROWLING, ROARING]
www.1TamilMV.us
[MONSTER ROARS]
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
[LIGHTNING CRACKLING]
[CREW CHATTERING]
[CHUCKLES]
[SHIP CREAKING]
- [ROARS]
- Diablos!
[ALL SHOUTING]
[♪♪♪]
- [GRUNTS]
- [SCREAMS]
- [GASPING]
[GRUNTING]
[GASPS]
- [SCREAMING]
- [GRUNTS]
- [DIABLOS ROARS]
- [YELLS]
[ROARING]
[SCREAMING]
[SCREAMS]
[YELLS]
[DIABLOS ROARS]
[♪♪♪]
SOLDIER [ON RECORDING]: Falcon
Main, this is Bravo Team.
Falcon Main, this is
Bravo Team. Do you copy?
Storm incoming.
Zero visibility.
Request immediate support.
[RAPID GUNFIRE]
Falcon Main, something's
in here with us.
Send immediate support.
[MAN SCREAMS, THEN STATIC]
[TAPE REWINDS]
Falcon Main,
this is Bravo Team.
Send immediate support.
MARSHALL [ECHOES]:
Ma'am.
- Ma'am.
- Marshall.
Link found something
half a klick ahead.
- Bravo Team?
- Think so.
Axe.
- With Steeler. Man the 50.
- AXE: Yes, boss.
All right, ladies.
Saddle up.
She's a woman,
but she still manages
to make that sound
like an insult.
- Get used to it.
- [ENGINE REVS]
[♪♪♪]
Captain. You see those markers?
Yeah, I see them.
Do you have any idea
what they are?
Sergeant Davis, I'm a Ranger,
not an archeologist.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Copy that.
[ON SPEAKER]
♪ Well, in North Carolina ♪
♪ Way back in the hills... ♪
- Axe!
- What?
- What are you listening to?
- George Jones.
Who the hell's that?
You're a philistine, Steeler.
Yes. Yes, I am.
[FLY BUZZING]
Damn, Marshall.
You got hella reflexes.
Fifteenth casualty today.
- Killing them.
- Take no prisoners, Davis.
♪ He brewed white lightnin'
Till the sun went down ♪
♪ And then you'd fill him a jug
And he'd pass it around ♪
♪ Mighty, mighty pleasin'
Pappy's corn squeezin' ♪
♪ Ssh, white lightnin' ♪
- Link, what'd you find?
- It's definitely Bravo Team.
But the tracks end here.
What were
Bravo Team traveling in?
Up-armored Humvee and a M-ATV.
That's 10 tons
of armored vehicle.
They don't just disappear.
Boss, we've got something.
Incoming. On your 12.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
- Where did that come from?
- Out of nowhere.
Bravo Team reported a storm
in their last transmission.
- Hostiles using it for cover?
- An ambush. Like in Helmand?
Let's not find out.
[♪♪♪]
REDCON-1. If there are hostiles
hiding behind that storm,
things might get kinetic.
Copy that.
[LIGHTNING CRACKLING]
Marshall,
what are you doing, bro?
In case I get my head blown off,
they can still tell who I am.
Ha-ha-ha!
Hardcore shit, cabrón.
- [GRUNTS]
- Damn!
MARSHALL:
Goddamn, that shit's close!
Link, you ever seen lightning
like this before?
No. Never.
But I feel pretty secure here
in this big steel box,
holding my metal gun.
Dash, on your 12!
Look at those markers!
What the hell is that?
- Watch out!
- Damn it!
Brace yourselves!
[ALL GROANING]
[GASPS]
[MARSHALL GROANS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER
OVER RADIO]
- [STATIC OVER RADIO]
- MARSHALL: Shit!
[ARTEMIS BREATHING HEAVILY]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
[ARTEMIS GASPS]
[ALL GROANING]
[ARTEMIS SHOUTS]
- [HIGH-PITCHED WHINING]
- [COUGHS]
[STATIC OVER RADIO]
[ARTEMIS GROANING]
[COUGHING]
[MARSHALL BREATHING HEAVILY]
Where the hell are we?
And what happened to the storm?
What the hell just happened?
[♪♪♪]
- ARTEMIS: Hey!
- Guys!
You okay?
Ugh, I'll survive.
Did we just get hit
by lightning?
- Steeler, you good?
- Never better.
[SPITS]
Where did
all this sand come from?
[ENGINE SPUTTERING]
[THUNDER RUMBLING
IN DISTANCE]
ARTEMIS: This isn't
right, none of it.
What the hell is that?
I don't see any structures
or mountains marked on this map.
According to this, the nearest
sand dune is 20 klicks away.
- How's that possible?
- AXE: Where the hell are we?
How did we get
so far from the road?
I don't know.
Axe, get on one of those dunes
- and set up an observation point.
- Yes, boss.
- ARTEMIS: Steeler!
- DPV will run. She's had worse.
- Marshall?
- GPS is fried, boss.
Radio and sat.
All I get is static.
Even the compass is screwed up.
Must've been the lightning.
Well, what do you wanna do?
Go analog. Navigate by the sun.
Make it back to base.
We hoof it if we have to.
Boss, that's a long hike.
Yeah, well,
we keep going till we get comms.
Then AWACS will call in support.
They'll send helos, maybe armor.
- [ENGINE STARTS, REVVING]
- [LAUGHS]
- ARTEMIS: Nice.
- Back in business.
- AXE [OVER RADIO]: Boss.
- Send it.
There's something
you gotta see.
[♪♪♪]
Up-armored DPV and a M-ATV.
It's Bravo Team.
V-formation. Move out.
- What do we do about them?
- When we get comms,
we'll call in recovery assets
to retrieve the bodies.
- What happened to them?
- Flamethrowers.
I don't think so.
Never seen a flamethrower
do this to a man.
Not even napalm burns that hot.
Ma'am?
It's glass.
Glass?
When sand melts,
it turns to glass.
How do you melt sand?
I don't know.
This shit is officially
above my pay grade.
Looks like they made a stand.
- Let off a lot of rounds.
- They didn't hit anything.
There's no bodies.
Maybe they took
the bodies with them?
- I've seen that before.
- LINK: Yeah.
- Well, that's just the thing.
- What do you see, Link?
Nothing.
No tracks anywhere.
Whoever did this,
they didn't leave a mark.
We need to get moving. Move out!
[♪♪♪]
Dark Star to Falcon.
Dark Star to Falcon, over.
Damn it. Lightning really
messed up the electronics, huh?
Not just the electronics.
- What do you mean?
- This isn't right.
Nothing about this is right.
That lightning,
it did something to us.
Captain knows
what she's doing, all right?
[RHYTHMIC POUNDING]
♪ They say that in the army
The pay is mighty fine ♪
♪ They give a hundred dollars
And take back 99 ♪
MARSHALL & ARTEMIS: ♪ They give a
hundred dollars And take back 99 ♪
♪ Oh, how I wanna go ♪
BOTH:
♪ But they won't let me go ♪
ALL:
♪ Home ♪
[♪♪♪]
♪ They say that in the army
The shoes are mighty fine ♪
♪ You ask for size 11
They give you size nine ♪
They give you a size nine ♪
♪ Oh, Lord, I wanna go
But they won't let me go ♪
♪ Home ♪
[♪♪♪]
DASH:
Jesus.
It has to be a dinosaur, right?
Saw a dinosaur in a museum
one time. It wasn't that big.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GASPS]
[YELLS INDISTINCTLY]
Hostile, 12 o'clock, 300 meters!
Cease fire! Cease fire!
- What's going on?
- It's just chalk.
[GROUND RUMBLING]
Chief?
[GRUNTS]
Diablos.
[SPITS]
On our 6!
STEELER:
What the hell is that?
Link, back in the vehicle.
Dash, Steeler, move, move, move!
[ENGINE STARTS]
ARTEMIS:
Fire!
[YELLS]
It's gaining on us!
[STEELER YELLS]
- AXE: You're caught.
- [GRUNTING]
[ROARS]
[GROWLING, ROARS]
- Come on, get out of here!
- No way!
- AXE: One...
- Holy...
...two, three!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Fire!
Give me your hand. Come on!
[AXE SCREAMS]
[ENGINE SPUTTERING]
- [YELLING]
- [ROARS]
Dash! Come on!
I'm trying!
Steeler!
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- Got it, got it!
Marshall, get in!
Let's go, big boy!
Give me your hand!
LINK:
Get inside!
Link, get the RPG!
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTS, BREATHING HEAVILY]
[STEELER COUGHS]
[GROANING]
[GASPS, COUGHING]
- [BOTH GROANING]
- [PANTING]
[GASPS]
[GURGLES]
Oh, my God.
[DIABLOS GROWLING]
[GROANING]
[ROARS]
[GRUNTS, EXHALES SHARPLY]
[ALL EXCLAIM]
[DIABLOS ROARS]
Fall back! Fall back!
Run for cover!
[♪♪♪]
MARSHALL:
Captain!
Come on!
MARSHALL:
Come on, boss!
[ROARING]
[GRUNTS]
[GROWLS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
MARSHALL:
I got it, I got it! Move, move!
Reloading!
[ROARS]
What was that thing?
What is that?
I told you. I told you.
That light,
it took us somewhere.
We need to get back.
We need to get back home.
- Stow it, Sergeant Davis.
- Oh, God. We're gonna die here.
Shut that shit up right now,
soldier. That's an order.
You see what it did
to Steeler and Axe?
Dash, hey.
I got three. You?
- What?
- Three mags left.
What does it matter?
Did you see that?
It matters
because we're soldiers.
And this is what we do.
We fight.
- Am I right?
- Rangers lead the way.
- You with me?
- Always, boss.
You're all crazy.
You know, I don't care
what the hell that thing is.
We do what we do best.
We fight and we survive.
No matter what the odds.
You got it?
- Yes, ma'am.
Loud and clear, ma'am.
Now, I got three left.
What about you?
- [SCREAMS]
- [GASPS]
[GROANS]
[♪♪♪]
[SHRIEKING]
Med pack!
- CPR, Marshall.
- On it.
- DASH: It's too late.
- Bullshit!
Don't die on me, Ranger.
Come on.
- Lack of pulse.
- Unacceptable. Try it again.
- I'm sorry.
- Shit! There's more of them!
DASH:
Come on! We have to go!
They're everywhere!
I'm sorry.
MARSHALL:
Master sergeant!
- Link!
- All right, on me!
- [HISSES]
- LINK: Let's move out!
MARSHALL:
Fall back, fall back!
[GUNFIRE CONTINUES]
[♪♪♪]
[DASH GASPS]
[GRUNTING]
[HISSING]
[GROANS]
MARSHALL:
Dash!
Come on!
Keep moving!
- [SCREAMS]
- Marshall!
[SCREAMS]
Go, go, go!
[MONSTER SHRIEKS]
LINK:
No!
[BOTH GRUNT]
[♪♪♪]
[GROANING]
[DASH & LINK YELLING
IN DISTANCE]
- ARTEMIS: Link.
- [DASH SCREAMS]
Dash.
[GRUNTS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[CHITTERING]
[♪♪♪]
[ARTEMIS SCREAMS]
[PANTING]
[GASPS]
[COUGHS]
[RETCHING]
[GASPING]
[BREATHING HOARSELY]
Dash.
[YELPS, RETCHES]
[SHUDDERING]
[GASPS]
[GRUNTS]
[MONSTER SHRIEKS]
[GROANS]
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[MONSTER SKITTERS IN DISTANCE]
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[♪♪♪]
[MONSTER HISSES IN DISTANCE]
[GASPS]
- LINK: You're alive.
- Link.
[GROANING]
What is it? What is it?
Pain in my chest!
I can't feel my arm.
Some sort of poison.
You just gotta work through it.
Come on. Let's move. Come on.
All right.
[♪♪♪]
- [GROANING]
- Oh, God.
Oh, no.
Captain.
All right, it's just
a little further. Let's go.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- Ugh! I can't move.
- Oh!
Okay, let me see.
- Let me see what it is.
- [GROANING]
[HISSES]
- [YELPS]
- [GROANING]
[GRUNTING]
- Go!
- [GRUNTS]
[LINK GROANING]
Oh, my God!
God, Link! No!
You gotta go!
[GROANING]
- [SCREAMS]
- Link!
[SCREAMING]
[YELPS]
[ROARS]
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
[GASPS]
[♪♪♪]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SCREAMING]
[SOBBING]
[ALL HISS]
[YELPS]
[GROANS]
[♪♪♪]
[RATTLING]
[WHISPERS]
Damn you.
[GROANS]
[SHOUTS]
Damn you!
[ALL HISS]
But I'm coming home.
[CHITTERING, ROARS]
[♪♪♪]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[GROANS]
[♪♪♪]
[THUNDER RUMBLING IN DISTANCE]
[GRUNTS]
[ROARS]
[GROWLING]
[♪♪♪]
[INSECTS BUZZING]
[RETCHES, COUGHS]
[GROANS]
[COUGHS]
[PEBBLES CLATTERING]
[GRUNTS]
[♪♪♪]
[CLATTERING CONTINUES]
[GASPS]
[SPEAKS IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
[GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
[GROANING]
[YELLS]
[GRUNTS, COUGHS]
[GRUNTS]
Nerscylla.
- Nerscylla!
- Get off me.
[SPEAKS IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
[♪♪♪]
[GROUND RUMBLING]
[SHRIEKS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GROANS]
[GARGLES]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[MONSTER SHRIEKS IN DISTANCE]
[MONSTER HISSES, CLATTERING]
- Nice life you've...
- [GROUND RUMBLING]
[SHUSHES]
[ALL SHRIEKING, HISSING]
[♪♪♪]
[CHANTING IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
[THUNDER RUMBLING IN DISTANCE]
[GRUNTS]
See how you like it.
[CHUCKLES]
Cheers.
[GRUNTS]
Oh!
Oh, you spiteful little bastard.
- [CHUCKLES]
- [YELLS]
[YELLS]
[SPEAKS IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
- Hey. How about that?
- [SPEAKS IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
Yeah. You don't like that, huh?
Not so funny now, huh?
- [SPEAKS IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
- [YELLS]
- [LAUGHS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
I'll kill you.
[YELLS]
[BOTH GROANING]
[SCREAMS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[♪♪♪]
[GROANING]
[MONSTERS HISSING]
Come on!
Push! Push!
[BOTH GROANING]
[PANTING]
[COUGHS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [GROANS]
Here.
I'm not your enemy.
Wait, wait.
Wait.
[GROANS]
One second. Look. Look.
Here.
Food.
Food. Here.
Take it.
[GRUNTS]
Here, give it to me.
Look, look.
Mmm.
Mmm, so good.
- Mmm.
- It's good, right?
Oh, wow.
Heh. Slow down. Okay, it's good.
- It's chocolate.
- Hmm?
- Chocolate.
Yeah, chocolate.
Chocolate.
- Choco...
- Chocolate!
- I don't have any more.
No, no more, no more, no more.
Look, look. Nothing.
I'm sorry.
[GRUNTS]
- [SPEAKS IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
- Oh.
Oh, my God. Thank you so much.
Oh, my God.
[SNIFFS]
Mmm.
Thank you.
Hey.
Wait! Where are you going?
[♪♪♪]
Wait!
[SPEAKS IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
Me and you go out there?
Yes. That lightning, I think
that's what brought me here.
I need to go there.
I need to get home.
That thing is still out there.
- Diablos.
Hey, over there...
I have weapons.
Uh...
[IMITATES GUNSHOTS]
Diablos... kssh!
[GRUNTS]
- What?
- [SPEAKS IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
[GRUMBLES]
[♪♪♪]
[COUGHING]
[SIGHS]
[MONSTER HISSES IN DISTANCE]
Ni trovi Nerscylla.
- What?
- Nerscylla.
No. We don't need
to go back in there.
We need to go out there.
Diablos.
Nerscylla.
Pssh! Diablo...
[SIGHS]
We poison it.
Smart.
To kill a monster,
you need a monster.
But how are we gonna get
one of those things?
What?
[♪♪♪]
ARTEMIS:
♪ They say that in the army ♪
♪ The coffee's mighty fine ♪
♪ It looks like muddy water
And tastes like turpentine ♪
♪ Oh, Lord, I wanna go
But they don't let me go ♪
♪ Home ♪
♪ They say that in the army
The men are mighty fine ♪
♪ To me
They look like hunchbacks ♪
♪ And sound like Frankenstein ♪
♪ Oh, Lord, I wanna go
But they won't let me go ♪
♪ Home ♪
[NERSCYLLA HISSES]
[♪♪♪]
[ROARS]
[GRUNTING]
Come on!
[YELLS]
[SHRIEKS]
Yes! Got it!
Next time, you're bait!
[ROCKS RATTLING]
"Ranger."
That's me.
[IMITATES GUNSHOT]
Ranger.
Yeah. Yeah.
[IMITATES ARROW SHOT]
Hunter.
Hunter. Ranger.
- Yeah. Yes.
- Hunter?
[LAUGHS]
[RIPS LOUDLY]
Velcro.
- Velcro.
- Yeah.
[WHISPERS]
Velcro. Velcro.
Okay. All right, all right.
That's enough. That's enough.
Oh, man.
- [COUGHS]
- [SIGHS]
Really trying
to get in here, huh?
[ALL HISSING, SHRIEKING]
[♪♪♪]
Is that your family?
[SPEAKS IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
[REPEATS ALIEN WORD]
Are you gonna see them?
Are you gonna go home?
Home?
I'm sorry.
Rathalos.
[♪♪♪]
Let's do this.
Hmm?
Never mind. Let's go.
[♪♪♪]
Ready!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[YELLS]
Whoa!
[GRUNTS]
- Yeah!
- Wow!
[♪♪♪]
[SPEAKS IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
[GRUNTS, CHUCKLES]
Ahh!
[CHUCKLES]
[SPEAKS IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
Wah!
Whoa!
[BOTH LAUGH]
- [GROANS]
- [LAUGHING]
What is that?
You gotta tell me about that.
You can't
just do that to somebody.
[SPEAKING IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
[♪♪♪]
Any second now.
- [ROARS]
- [YELLS IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
[ROARS]
[♪♪♪]
Stop!
Bait!
[♪♪♪]
[PANTING]
[YELLS]
[ROARS]
[GROANS]
[GRUNTS]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
- [ROARING]
- Yeah!
[♪♪♪]
[GROANS]
[ROARS]
[RAPID GUNFIRE]
[ROARING]
Shit!
[GROANING]
[DIABLOS ROARING]
[YELLING]
[SHRIEKS]
[ROARS]
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTING]
- [YELLS]
- [SHRIEKS]
[SCREAMS]
[PANTING]
[♪♪♪]
[THUNDER CRASHING IN DISTANCE]
[WIND WHISTLING]
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GROANS]
[COUGHS]
[GASPS]
[GROANS]
[LIGHTNING CRACKLING]
[COUGHS]
- [ARTEMIS GRUNTS]
- [COUGHS]
Come on!
Watch over him!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[♪♪♪]
[GASPS]
[MUTTERS INDISTINCTLY]
[GRUNTS]
You're welcome.
[♪♪♪]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Wow.
[CREATURES LOWING]
Apceros.
- Apceros.
- Yeah.
Okay. Okay. They eat grass.
Water. Water.
[ROARING]
[YELLS]
Bait.
[LAUGHING]
Bait?
You're funny.
Know what I'm gonna do next time
you're dying in the desert?
Nothing.
[♪♪♪]
That smells good.
- Catch Cephalos.
- I'll eat anything at this point.
[LIGHTNING CRACKLING]
Home.
Yeah. My way home.
I hope.
Chocolate.
[BLOWING]
[CHUCKLES]
Mmm.
Mmm, chocolate. Mmm.
So good.
- Mmm.
What's that?
Whoa!
[BOTH LAUGH]
All right.
Uh-uh-uh...
[GULPS]
[CHUCKLES]
- Whoo! Whoo!
- Chocolate.
No, no, no.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
- Chocolate.
- Not chocolate.
[EXHALES SHARPLY, SHUDDERS]
[THUNDER RUMBLES IN DISTANCE]
[♪♪♪]
[WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY]
[ROARING]
- What's going on?
- Rathalos.
You said that before.
What the hell is
a Rathalos?
[APCEROS BELLOWING]
[GASPS]
[YELLS]
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS]
[ROARING]
Whoa!
[GRUNTING]
[YELLING IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
[HUNTER GROANS]
[WINCH CLICKS]
[GRUNTS]
[SIGHS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Thank you.
Don't thank me yet.
[♪♪♪]
[LEA WHISTLING]
Enjoying the show?
[WHISTLING CONTINUES]
Whoo!
[IN ALIEN LANGUAGE] This one
must have come from the sky.
[SPEAKS IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
[BELL RINGING]
[♪♪♪]
[LIQUID BUBBLING]
[YOWLING]
What?
[SPEAKS IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
[GROWLS]
- [MEOWS]
- What is that?
Palico.
[MEOWS SOFTLY]
My friend tells me
I misjudged you...
that I might even
owe you an apology.
Just don't hold your breath.
Why did you put me in chains?
What are you so afraid of?
Your world...
and what it could do to mine.
You aren't the first
to cross over from your world.
There were others.
A long time ago.
That's how you speak
my language?
- Mmm, I made a study of it.
- What happened to me?
How did I get here?
I believe that the answers
we both seek lie here.
At the peak of that mountain
lies the Sky Tower.
Remnants
of an ancient civilization.
Very advanced. Very dangerous.
It is said
that the Ancients knew
how to travel
between both worlds.
I believe that is the purpose
of the Sky Tower.
That is what brought you here.
What happened
to this ancient civilization?
They destroyed themselves.
Their technology turned on them.
You think my world
had something to do with it.
I suspect. But an open gateway
between our two worlds
was catastrophic once.
I intend to make sure
that doesn't happen again.
We were on our way
to investigate the Sky Tower
when we strayed
into the Diablos.
That's where I lost
my friend here.
Tending to the wounded
and repairing the ship
was our first priority.
But now we resume our mission.
The Ancients would
guard their technology
with the most fearsome
of creatures,
a Rathalos.
Almost impossible to kill.
Their only weakness is
just before they breathe fire.
You help us
with the battle ahead,
perhaps we can help you
get home.
[PURRS]
[MEOWS]
What's the matter?
You don't have cats
in your world?
Hey!
You been drinking
from my mug again?
[MEOWS SOFTLY]
[SIGHS]
We leave at dawn.
And don't keep me waiting.
I hate waiting.
[♪♪♪]
[LIGHTNING CRACKLING
IN DISTANCE]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[CREW CHEERING]
So? You ready?
We got a hard climb ahead of us.
[PURRING SOFTLY]
[BLOWS KISS]
[CHUCKLES]
LEA:
Come on!
[HUNTER SPEAKS
IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
[♪♪♪]
[LIGHTNING CRACKLING]
We believe that the lava powers
the machinery within the tower.
It's controlling the storm.
Exactly.
It's creating a gateway to your
world, but it looks unstable.
Let's go.
[♪♪♪]
[GLASS CRACKING]
[IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
It's glass.
Estas bone Rathalos.
Rathalos.
[SPEAKS IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
Prepare yourself.
Remember, they're weak
just before they breathe fire.
[WINGS FLAPPING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [GASPS]
- [SHUSHES]
[SCREAMING]
[HUNTER SPEAKS
IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
[♪♪♪]
[ROARS]
[GROWLING]
Hey, ugly!
[YELLS]
[GROANS]
[GRUNTS]
- [ROARS]
- [YELLS]
[YELLS]
[♪♪♪]
- [ROARS]
- [YELLS]
[YELLING]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLING]
- [ROARS]
- [YELLS]
[YELLS]
[SHRIEKS]
[♪♪♪]
[YELLING]
[GRUNTING]
[GROANS]
[YELLS]
[GASPS]
[GROANS SOFTLY]
[DISTORTED THUNDER RUMBLES]
[WINGS FLAPPING]
[FLAPPING INCREASES SPEED]
[HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING]
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS]
It's okay! It's okay.
You're safe now! Get the medic!
Captain Artemis?
Let's get her inside! Up!
Let's go! Let's go!
[DISTORTED] Captain,
we've been searching for you.
What the hell is she wearing?
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING
OVER RADIO]
Falcon Main, this is Red Wolf.
PILOT [OVER RADIO]: We've
made contact with Dark Star.
We have a lone survivor.
I say again, a lone survivor.
Ground forces are
securing the area.
Copy that, Red Wolf.
Captain.
Can you hear me?
[ECHOING]
Captain?
Captain Artemis?
Where are the rest of your men?
- My men?
- Yes.
[IN REGULAR VOICE] Where
are the rest of Alpha Team?
OFFICER [OVER RADIO]:
Copy that.
[LIGHTNING CRACKLING]
[GRUNTS SOFTLY]
- [ROARS]
- [SCREAMS]
ROARK:
We're under attack!
[GASPS]
[HIGH-PITCHED WHINING]
- [GASPS]
- [GROANS]
[GROANS]
[♪♪♪]
Aim for the belly!
THE ADMIRAL:
A Rathalos.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SCREAMS]
[SOLDIER YELLS INDISTINCTLY
OVER RADIO]
Load!
Fire!
[GASPS]
[SOLDIERS SCREAMING]
[ALL SCREAMING]
No! No!
[SCREAMS]
[♪♪♪]
[SHRIEKS]
[ROARS]
[MOUTH CRACKLES]
No!
It's coming right for us!
Evade!
[♪♪♪]
OFFICER [OVER RADIO]: We're on Channel 5.
Interference is...
My God.
[ROARS]
[METAL SQUEALING]
[GROANS]
[♪♪♪]
[ROARS]
[GROWLING]
[SHRIEKS]
- [RATHALOS SHRIEKS]
- [ARTEMIS YELLS]
[GROANS]
[ROARS]
[GROWLS]
Come on!
- [FLARE SIZZLES]
- [SCREAMS]
[GROANS]
[MOUTH CRACKLES]
[PANTING]
I got you.
[ROARING]
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTS]
[SHRIEKS]
[♪♪♪]
My friend.
[IN ALIEN LANGUAGE] Thought
you might need a little help.
Yeah, I...
still don't understand you, man.
Oh, yeah.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Friends.
Yeah, thank you.
Min misa chocolate?
I don't have
any more chocolate.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
Think fast.
- You're here.
- We came to help.
We can't have monsters
from my world attacking yours.
[LIGHTNING CRACKLING]
It's starting again.
We don't have much time.
There's going to be
another attack.
[ROARS]
We have to get back.
We have
to shut the Sky Tower down.
Let's try
to live through this first.
Copy that.
[ROARS]
[ALL YELL]
[YELLING]
[ROARS]
[♪♪♪]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[RATHALOS ROARING]
[MEOWS]
[GROWLS, YOWLS]
[♪♪♪]
www.1TamilMV.us